# Igirimbabazi Kayumba Regis

❖Email: Kayumbaregis03@gmail.com ❖Tel: 452880885 ❖Warsaw, PL

Portfolio: https://regiskayumba.vercel.app/

**SUMMARY** 

Computer engineering student, Experienced in various fields such as IT support, customer support, HR, sales, troubleshooting, hardware/software maintenance, and network configuration. Currently advancing skills through studies. Fluent in English, French, and Kinyarwanda. I'm very reliable and adaptable. To see my projects, click on the link above.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Rwanda Agriculture Board (RAB)

Nov. 2022 – Sep. 2023

HR Assistant/junior IT support/logistics officer

Kigali, RW

- As an HR assistant, I provided clerical support to the HR manager and Administrative Support. To improve the HR department's efficiency.
- **Subsidiary responsibility #1**: As JR. IT support I Performed system maintenance and updates as appropriate. I provided staff with technical support, including troubleshooting operating systems, applications, and network issues, answering questions regarding application use, and installing software.
- **subsidiary responsibility #2**: I also had more responsibility as a logistics officer, I oversaw the replacement of all unserviceable office equipment, the Disposal of scrap and salvage, and the whole life cycle of all office equipment, I was also responsible for the Management and supply of fuel for organization's errands.

Kin Clothing Store Aug. 2021 – Apr. 2022

Customer Support

Kigali, RW

- As customer support I provided helpful information, answered questions, responded to complaints, and resolved customer's issues with empathy and a problem-solving mindset.
- I undertook the processing of orders and transactions for customers.

Kin Electronic Store

May. 2022 - Nov. 2022

Salesman

Kigali, RW

- As a salesman I provided information about products and promotions, answered inquiries, handled inventories, and kept the store organized. I undertook the processing of orders and transactions for customers.
- I Maintained regular communication with customers to address inquiries regarding the product.
- Using my technical expertise, I repaired damaged gadgets and computer products in stock.

#### Vision Technology

Sept. 2021 – Oct. 2021

IT support

Kigali, RW

 I completed an academic internship where I undertook several key responsibilities I configured and installed CCTV cameras and networks, troubleshooting repairing, and maintenance of IT office equipment like Computers, laptops, printers, photocopiers, etc...

### **EDUCATION**

Vistula University

Oct. 2023 – present

Computer Engineering

Warsaw, PL

SOS Herman Gmeiner Technical High School

Feb. 2018 - Jul. 2021

computer Systems, Networking, and Telecommunications

Kigali, RW

## **SKILLS, INTERESTS & LANGUAGES**

- Skills: C#, Java, Assembly, HTML/CSS, SQL, Active directory, windows server, Ticketing systems, VMware,
  Oracle VirtualBox, Operating Systems, Network configuration, Office 365, Data backup,
  Troubleshooting/Problem-solving, Computer hardware & software repair and maintenance, learning agility,
  Communication, Customer service, Analysis of technical issues, sales, and persuasion, etc...
- languages: English (Fluent), French (Intermediate), Polish (beginner) and Kinyarwanda (Native).

I consent to the processing of my personal data for recruitment purposes under the Personal Data Protection Act and GDPR.